# **OLUWAJOLASUN OLUFEMI JAIYESIMI**

#406, 815 – 4 Avenue SW, Calgary, Alberta. T2P 3G8 · 674-637-9575 jolasunjaiyesimi@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/oluwajolasun/ · www.oluwajolasun.com

A determined and highly organized individual, with a strong work ethic and proven ability to take responsibility and work under pressure with little or no supervision. I have gained relevant experience by working in a fast-paced environment, working with people as a team, approaching internal/external customers to satisfy their needs and hitting required targets.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **MAY 2020 - PRESENT**

## FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER/FREELANCE DURAG DESIGNER AND MAKER

- Handling all verbal and written communications between hosting companies, clients, and vendors.
- Meeting with the prospective clients to review website and gather the client specifications for new or existing websites.
- Built, designed, and maintained websites for businesses using WordPress CMS, HTML, CSS, JavaScript (React), Bootstrap, Material UI etc.
- Designing, making, and selling of durags, a fashion accessory for customers

View website for portfolio at <u>oluwajolasun.com</u> and for durag at <u>jayragbyjj.com</u> built by me

#### **MAY 2017 - JULY 2018**

## WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE,

THORN BAKER INDUSTRIAL, LOUGHBOROUGH, UNITED KINGDOM.

- Performed all warehouse laborer duties including picking, packing, counting, record keeping, and maintaining a clean area.
- Consistently maintained picking/packing speeds in the 95th percentile.
- Picked all orders with 100% accuracy despite high speeds.
- Maintained a clean work area, meeting 98% of inspection requirements.

## **JULY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018**

#### **BAR & LOGISTICS SUPERVISOR,**

LOUGHBOROUGH UNIVERSITY STUDENTS' UNION, LOUGHBOROUGH, UNITED KINGDOM

- To communicate clearly with customers who are under the influence of alcohol.
- Responsible for the upkeep of the bar and maintaining professional standards throughout the night
- Financial control and stock maintenance
- Setting up the venue as advised by the managers
- Allocating breaks to staff and ensuring they are providing excellent customer service
- Using radios to communicate with managers and securities
- Nominated and awarded as the best logistics staff/supervisor for the 2018 staff awards

## **EDUCATION**

**MAY 2021 - ONGOING** 

## MENG (HONS), SOFTWARE ENGINEERING,

UNIVERSITY OF CALGARY, ALBERTA, CANADA

- Programming Fundamentals for Data Engineers
- Principles of Software Development.
- Data Structure and Algorithms

# **SEPTEMBER 2015 – JULY 2018**

# BENG (HONS), ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING,

LOUGHBOROUGH UNIVERSITY, LEICESTERSHIRE, UNITED KINGDOM

- Overall Second-Class Honors, Upper Division
- Finished my second year of the university with an overall Second class upper
- Finished my first year of the university with an overall Second class upper
- Final year project, building a cheap radio by software defined radio algorithms using MATLAB (Simulink) using an RTL-SDR with an overall 2:1 in the written deliverable and the Viva voce.
- Proficiency in areas of Microsoft Office, including Word, Excel and PowerPoint.

Modules including Fast Transient Sensors, Software Engineering, Electromagnetism, Digital and state space control, Bioelectricity, Mathematics, Communications, Circuits, Electronics.

## **SKILLS**

- Customer service skills
- High-level IT skills
- Communication
- Organization
- Social Media Marketing

- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Creativity

#### **ACTIVITIES**

- Traveling and exploring new places.
- Listening to music, hanging out with friends, playing any sport.
- Learning new things about different culture.
- Maintenance/assistant hostel prefect boy
- Gold and silver medalist for interhouse sports (2012-2013)
- Certified windows XP OS installer (2011)

## REFERENCES

References are available on request.